<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<REGION id="the_pacific">
  

  <MESSAGES>
    

    <POST id="61486435">
      
	
      <TIMESTAMP>1773021609</TIMESTAMP>
      
	
      <NATION>new_pacific_order</NATION>
      
	
      <STATUS>0</STATUS>
      
	
      <LIKES>0</LIKES>
      
	
      <MESSAGE><![CDATA[Greetings [nation]gamma-7[/nation], [nation]gamma-3[/nation], [nation]gamma-1[/nation], [nation]the_nation_of_uranda[/nation], [nation]noble_causes[/nation], [nation]al-shakra[/nation], [nation]united_socialist_of_england[/nation], [nation]test_7_inner_strilan_souopia[/nation], [nation]test_5_inner_strilan_souopia[/nation], [nation]the_royal_empire_of_the_duck[/nation]!

Welcome to NationStates and the Pacific! The Pacific is the oldest region on NationStates, home to a vibrant community that has a place for just about everything and everyone. The Regional Message Board, especially, is an active hub of roleplay with our [url=https://www.nationstates.net/page=dispatch/id=2622699][b]Commonverse RP[/b][/url]. You can also consider joining [b][url=https://www.nationstates.net/page=dispatch/id=1810625]our military, writing World Assembly resolutions or Issues, or collecting cards[/b][/url]. Make sure you've [url=https://www.nationstates.net/page=dispatch/id=1589991][b]joined the World Assembly and endorsed our delegate[/b][/url] [nation]Pasybfic[/nation]!

[i]This is an automated message.[/i]]]></MESSAGE>
      

    </POST>
    

    <POST id="61486447">
      
	
      <TIMESTAMP>1773021900</TIMESTAMP>
      
	
      <NATION>slovensknia</NATION>
      
	
      <STATUS>0</STATUS>
      
	
      <LIKES>0</LIKES>
      
	
      <MESSAGE><![CDATA[President of Slovensknia Konrad Guðmundurs Condition is unknown 
But as of Now acting President Viktor Stálheim has taken power ]]></MESSAGE>
      

    </POST>
    

    <POST id="61486478">
      
	
      <TIMESTAMP>1773022483</TIMESTAMP>
      
	
      <NATION>communist_freedom</NATION>
      
	
      <STATUS>0</STATUS>
      
	
      <LIKES>1</LIKES>
      
	
      <LIKERS>slovensknia</LIKERS>
      
	
      <MESSAGE><![CDATA[[quote=the_status-quo;61485546]Hi, I am a reincarnation of a long dead nation seeing if this interests me again.[/quote]
hello]]></MESSAGE>
      

    </POST>
    

    <POST id="61486773">
      
	
      <TIMESTAMP>1773028810</TIMESTAMP>
      
	
      <NATION>new_pacific_order</NATION>
      
	
      <STATUS>0</STATUS>
      
	
      <LIKES>0</LIKES>
      
	
      <MESSAGE><![CDATA[Greetings [nation]bastidas[/nation], [nation]catacataca[/nation], [nation]trillandua[/nation]!

Welcome to NationStates and the Pacific! The Pacific is the oldest region on NationStates, home to a vibrant community that has a place for just about everything and everyone. The Regional Message Board, especially, is an active hub of roleplay with our [url=https://www.nationstates.net/page=dispatch/id=2622699][b]Commonverse RP[/b][/url]. You can also consider joining [b][url=https://www.nationstates.net/page=dispatch/id=1810625]our military, writing World Assembly resolutions or Issues, or collecting cards[/b][/url]. Make sure you've [url=https://www.nationstates.net/page=dispatch/id=1589991][b]joined the World Assembly and endorsed our delegate[/b][/url] [nation]Pasybfic[/nation]!

[i]This is an automated message.[/i]]]></MESSAGE>
      

    </POST>
    

    <POST id="61486910">
      
	
      <TIMESTAMP>1773033045</TIMESTAMP>
      
	
      <NATION>novoblupolia</NATION>
      
	
      <STATUS>0</STATUS>
      
	
      <LIKES>2</LIKES>
      
	
      <LIKERS>northern_norkelia:bahalbha_island</LIKERS>
      
	
      <MESSAGE><![CDATA[[quote=novoblupolia;61337247][spoiler=Classified Material: Research Entry #1]
2:03 pm. Finally got my hands on this damn virus that's causing trouble in Norkelia. Had to pull a few strings to get it smuggled across the border in a special container disguised as soda cans. Risks were minimized, and nobody got infected on it's way to me. But with how the situation has been progressing, more cases are only a matter of time. I've immediately begun conducting analysis of it.

5:47 pm. Initial analysis confirms what I thought - this may take several weeks, at the very least. It indeed causes inflammation and chemical reactiong that prevents contact with oxygen within the human organism. My initial research will be aimed at minimizing, or possibly even eliminating the fatality rate of the disease. May take around a couple weeks to get there.

9:30 pm. Skipped dinner. Spent the last 3 hours double-checking the AI contribution to systematization of the data. No misinputs, thank God. But the numbers paint a dire picture. While in Novoblupolia, the lockdowns should keep cases within the bounds of quadriple digits per week for the forseeable future in the worst case scenario, in Norkelia, it will be way worse. Kids and Seniors, as well as people with lung and heart conditions are at most risk. I've already sent a leak of this information to Norkelian press through anonymous sources. 

11:02 pm. Warpping up the first day of research. Had to seal the virus sample beyond several layers of defense. I have also extracted a sample of my own blood, to see how the virus would interact with blood plasma when it is separated from the rest of the body. Haemoglobin molecules are, as I thought, the primary target of the virus. Therefore, it appears that the treatment injection formula must either figure out a way to prevent the chemical reaction that causes the oxygen delivery to become dysfunctional, or it must provide the organism with a new type of red blood cells, with protections already provided against the virus. I'll be working on both options. It'll take more time, but it's foolish to put all my eggs in one basket.

- B.W.R.[/spoiler]

[spoiler=ping][nation]Northern Norkelia[/nation][/spoiler][/quote]
[spoiler=Classified Material: Research Entry #20]
1: 23 am. The syringe is in my hand. I have rolled up the sleeve on my other hand. Time to test out this prototype. Lisa insisted I test it out on hamsters or guinea pigs, but nothing justifies animal cruelty when I have a perfect test subject in myself. Can't help but chuckle as I fill it up with the prototype vaccine. The math and chemistry analysis checks out. It should work. I'll have my equipment track every aspect of my health for the next week. If all goes well, I'm leaking this formula to research centers.

Alrighty then, virus. Come to papa.[/spoiler]]]></MESSAGE>
      

    </POST>
    

    <POST id="61486980">
      
	
      <TIMESTAMP>1773036010</TIMESTAMP>
      
	
      <NATION>new_pacific_order</NATION>
      
	
      <STATUS>0</STATUS>
      
	
      <LIKES>0</LIKES>
      
	
      <MESSAGE><![CDATA[Greetings [nation]ritobeca[/nation], [nation]noxotria[/nation], [nation]geniusus[/nation]!

Welcome to NationStates and the Pacific! The Pacific is the oldest region on NationStates, home to a vibrant community that has a place for just about everything and everyone. The Regional Message Board, especially, is an active hub of roleplay with our [url=https://www.nationstates.net/page=dispatch/id=2622699][b]Commonverse RP[/b][/url]. You can also consider joining [b][url=https://www.nationstates.net/page=dispatch/id=1810625]our military, writing World Assembly resolutions or Issues, or collecting cards[/b][/url]. Make sure you've [url=https://www.nationstates.net/page=dispatch/id=1589991][b]joined the World Assembly and endorsed our delegate[/b][/url] [nation]Pasybfic[/nation]!

[i]This is an automated message.[/i]]]></MESSAGE>
      

    </POST>
    

    <POST id="61487082">
      
	
      <TIMESTAMP>1773039361</TIMESTAMP>
      
	
      <NATION>nieuw_stenenland</NATION>
      
	
      <STATUS>0</STATUS>
      
	
      <EDITED>1773039426</EDITED>
      
	
      <LIKES>0</LIKES>
      
	
      <MESSAGE><![CDATA[[quote=bahalbha_island;61486047][table][tr][td][b]DAILY QUESTION[/b][/td][/tr]
[tr][td]9th of March, 2026 | No.389[/td][/tr]
[tr][td]&#128924; Are there any recreational drugs which were invented in or are only found in your nation? [/td][/tr][/table][/quote]
There are three types of recreation drug made from endemic flora. Kawhi leaves, a mild stimulant; Kehlun Gulway a dissociative hallucinogen extracted from mushrooms; and Dhaan Kehwi, another fungi made into a powerful psychedelic. 

[spoiler=factbook excerpts]Kawhi is an endemic species of flowering deciduous shrub, which grows in shaded riparian habitats throughout the island, recognizable by their toothy-edged rhomboid-shaped leaves, which are typically no more than two centimetres in length and no more than one and a half centimetres wide. These leaves are chewed as a mild stimulant drug; specifically an entactogen. More descriptively called an empathogen or connectogen, this variety of drug induces feelings of emotional connection, empathy, communion, and openness. Given the easy availability of the leaves in warmer seasons, they are often chewed during social events, or as an aphrodisiac, or simply as a more enjoyable alternative to sobriety. The leaves can also be crushed to extract their sap, which is then diluted with water, mixed with Hayka syrup and fermented to create a drink called Kawhi Gulway which is much more potent and intoxicating than the fresh leaves, and which can importantly be stored and consumed during the winter.

-

StenenLand False Milk-Caps are a genus of at least 17 identified species of mushroom-producing ectomycorrhizal fungi, characterized by the inverted conical shapes of their mushroom caps and the milky latex fluid their musrhooms secrete as a defence mechanism when damaged. They grow in symbiotic relationships with a variety of plant species, connecting to their root systems underground through mycelium networks. Several species are edible, but a few are toxic.
The most famous species is the Gikhliakwa Kehlun - Lactarius Falsus Rosus, which grows primarily in the Highlands Kahu or Groen Valley. Its dried latex has long been harvested by Waioru and dissolved into a fermented solution made with sap from the leaves of the Kawhi plant, a natural stimulant, diluted in water, to produce a dissociative hallucinogen called Kehlun Gulway. This is a rather powerful drug which generally causes a reduction in sensory awareness, especially reducing pain and other unpleasant sensations, such that it was used as an analgesic painkiller in traditional Waioru medicine. In recreational use, it causes dream-like euphoric and dissociative effects, with hallucinations sometimes occurring at high doses. Side effects include loss of consciousness, and especially when too much is consumed, seizures or comas, which can be potentially lethal. It is also capable of becoming addictive if consumed regularly. Historically, Waioru were unable to produce it in large enough quantities to sustain addiction, but since the 1980s, it has been cultivated in greenhouses full of symbiotic plants, to produce the drug in larger quantities, leading to numerous cases of addiction, though it has never been remotely as common as international hard drugs.

-

The main fungus (from Dhaan Kehwi forests, where species of moss, tree, and fungi have closely symbiotic relationships), also referred to as simply Dhaan Kehwi, had multiple uses based on preparation method and what part of the fungus is used; one being medicinal, strengthening the immune system, including against cancer, another being adaptogenic, helping the body adapt to stress, including from depression, while also helping against cancer. The most noteworthy use however, is as a powerful psychedelic drug, using the aboveground growths (in this use it is still adaptogenic, though less strongly). This fungus also contains mycotoxins, and if prepared or stored wrong, or consumed with alcohol, the products thereof can be harmful, causing kidney damage and risk of Cholinergic crisis (muscles stop responding properly leading to flaccid paralysis, respiratory failure). It also causes gastrointestinal irritation, vomiting, and nausea in some people (very rarely in those from local tribes).[/spoiler]]]></MESSAGE>
      

    </POST>
    

    <POST id="61487123">
      
	
      <TIMESTAMP>1773040539</TIMESTAMP>
      
	
      <NATION>asukalia</NATION>
      
	
      <STATUS>0</STATUS>
      
	
      <LIKES>1</LIKES>
      
	
      <LIKERS>new_klothia</LIKERS>
      
	
      <MESSAGE><![CDATA[[b]Somewhere...Usizo...[/b]
With Asukalian support flooding in, and the boost in numbers following the ANW collapse, the ALW prepared for a general offensive into Usizo province. They a had secured a foothold in the North of Okusha, now it was time to carve out a distinct territory. The ALW formed a corridor along the northern border of Okosha, to the border of Usizo province, as well as a securing the road south to the conquered FOB. The offensive against the smaller rebel groups was about to begin. 

Through the entire northern province the ALW swept, using their tanks, technicals, and other armoured vehicles to overwhelm the disparate forces of the OCF and SCF. The movement of the other forces was tracked and marked down, with technicals directed to sweep up patrols and forces. From one end of the province they moved to the border. Executing bandits and criminals they found along the way. In their wake they provided energy and clean water amenities to those in the liberated villages. As the groups faced serious resistance they dissolved, unable to fight against the better equipped, better trained, and better informed forces. To symbolise their complete dominance in the province, a small contingent scaled Mt. Phezulusec, broadcasting the flag raising live online. Much of Usizo was soon under ALW control.

[b]Somewhere... Wengala...[/b]
As the ANW collapsed, the Free Air Force was tasked with destroying the remains of their armoured reserves, airstrikes on barracks and warehouses intensified, precision munitions, often paired with drones flying overhead guiding with lasers made short work of abandoned SAM sites, tank sheds, and depots. All with the aim of giving the ALW total armoured supremacy. 

[b]ALW Force Analysis:[/b]
[b]Soldiers:[/b]
&gt;13,000 Soldiers
Equipped with a G-16 each, Officers usually have a sidearm or SMG (usually of the PG-17 or MPX), each squad has a MG60 or MG249, and may be equipped with a G82. Most squads have between 2-3 AT-4s, and may occasionally have grenade launchers. MG2s, MM81s are usually held at the company level, or with the supply vehicle (usually a transport technical).

[b]Artillery[/b]
x40 M119A3 Light Artillery Gun
x4 MLRS Launchers

[b]Vehicles:[/b]
x22 Type 60A3s with ERA mounted. (x4 permanently deployed in Khule).
x72 JLTVs
x80 M939
Unknown number of technicals (whether transport, armoured, or armed), presumed in hundreds.

[b]Aircraft (fixed and rotor):[/b]
x12 F-4T 2000s. 
x4 MH-6 Helicopters.

[spoiler=ping]
[nation]Wengala[/nation]
[nation]New Klothia[/nation][/spoiler]]]></MESSAGE>
      

    </POST>
    

    <POST id="61487200">
      
	
      <TIMESTAMP>1773043209</TIMESTAMP>
      
	
      <NATION>new_pacific_order</NATION>
      
	
      <STATUS>0</STATUS>
      
	
      <LIKES>0</LIKES>
      
	
      <MESSAGE><![CDATA[Greetings [nation]rado_aazazaazzaazzzazaa[/nation], [nation]bascita[/nation], [nation]rado_aazazaazazzazzaaaz[/nation], [nation]rado_aazazaazazzazaazaa[/nation], [nation]sylqara[/nation], [nation]kryzmar[/nation], [nation]rado_aazazaazazazzzaazz[/nation], [nation]rado_aazazaazazazazzzzaz[/nation], [nation]rado_aazazaazazazazaazz[/nation], [nation]rado_aazazaazazazazaaza[/nation], [nation]rado_aazazaazazaazazazz[/nation], [nation]rado_aazazaazazaazazaza[/nation], [nation]fjolqara[/nation], [nation]basvara[/nation], [nation]bryndahra[/nation], [nation]calista_galic[/nation]!

Welcome to NationStates and the Pacific! The Pacific is the oldest region on NationStates, home to a vibrant community that has a place for just about everything and everyone. The Regional Message Board, especially, is an active hub of roleplay with our [url=https://www.nationstates.net/page=dispatch/id=2622699][b]Commonverse RP[/b][/url]. You can also consider joining [b][url=https://www.nationstates.net/page=dispatch/id=1810625]our military, writing World Assembly resolutions or Issues, or collecting cards[/b][/url]. Make sure you've [url=https://www.nationstates.net/page=dispatch/id=1589991][b]joined the World Assembly and endorsed our delegate[/b][/url] [nation]Pasybfic[/nation]!

[i]This is an automated message.[/i]]]></MESSAGE>
      

    </POST>
    

    <POST id="61487213">
      
	
      <TIMESTAMP>1773043638</TIMESTAMP>
      
	
      <NATION>new_klothia</NATION>
      
	
      <STATUS>0</STATUS>
      
	
      <LIKES>0</LIKES>
      
	
      <MESSAGE><![CDATA[International Message - Greeting (Unprofessional)
[nation=long]New Klothia[/nation]

Morning or good day everyone! Ima try to respond to messages, as its a bit harder today to actually write a good response. 

Anyway have a productive and Peaceful day!]]></MESSAGE>
      

    </POST>
    

  </MESSAGES>
  

</REGION>
